<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<GenresList>
    <Genres>
        <name>Fiction</name>
        <SubGenresList>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>Romance</name>
                <description>
                    Oh romance, how could we ever resist you?
                    The genre that makes your heart all warm and fuzzy focuses on the love story of the main
                    protagonists. This world of fiction is extremely wide-reaching in and of itself, as it has a variety
                    of sub-genres including: contemporary romance, historical, paranormal, and the steamier erotica. If
                    you're in need of any suggestions, we've got a list of the best romances of all time and the top
                    picks of the year.
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>Comic Book or Graphic Novel</name>
                <description>The stories in comic books and graphic novels are presented to the reader through engaging,
                    sequential narrative art (illustrations and typography) that's either presented in a specific design
                    or the traditional panel layout you find in comics. With both, you'll often find the dialogue
                    presented in the tell-tale "word balloons" next to the respective characters.
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>Historical Fiction</name>
                <description>These books are based in a time period set in the past decades, often against the backdrop
                    of significant (real) historical events.
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>Horror</name>
                <description>Meant to cause discomfort and fear for both the character and readers, horror writers often
                    make use of supernatural and paranormal elements in morbid stories that are sometimes a little too
                    realistic. The master of horror fiction? None other than Stephen King
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>Literary Fiction</name>
                <description>Though it can be seen as a broad genre that encompasses many others, literary fiction
                    refers to the perceived artistic writing style of the author. Their prose is meant to evoke deep
                    thought through stories that offer personal or social commentary on a particular theme.
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
        </SubGenresList>
    </Genres>
    <Genres>
        <name>Non Fiction</name>
        <SubGenres>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>Biographies And Memoir</name>
                <description>A memoir tells readers about significant moments in the life of the author. Memoirs are
                    sometimes confused with autobiographies since they are both written from the same perspective.
                    However, what differentiates the two is that memoirs may be written about a shorter period of time,
                    such as a specific event or experience in the writer’s life.

                    Both biographies and autobiographies focus on retelling a life story, but the two genres are
                    different. Autobiographies are written about and by the author. Biographies are third-person
                    narratives, where the author tells someone else’s story (while still remaining accurate and
                    factual). Unlike autobiographies, the subject of the story can be living or dead when writing
                    biographies.
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>History</name>
                <description>History nonfiction writing involves recounting a historical event or specific time period.
                    While authors can frame how the information is presented, all information presented in history
                    nonfiction must be verifiable, factual, and historically accurate.
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
            <SubGenres>
                <name>Self Development &amp; Hobbies</name>
                <description>The self-help genre is surprisingly (or perhaps not!) one of the most popular categories on
                    nonfiction. Here, authors can teach readers anything from new skills, how to manage finance,
                    maintaining happiness, and even parenting or starting a new business.
                </description>
            </SubGenres>
        </SubGenres>
    </Genres>
</GenresList>
